poojitha yadavalli

Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India



linkedin.com/in/poojitha-yadavalli-77aa24150



poojithareddyyadavalli@gmail.com

Summary

I am a kind of person passionate about learning new Technology. I worked with technologies related to Web Development like Bootstrap and Angular. I can adopt to new environments and handle stress with ease. I am blessed with the ability to grasp things faster.

Experience



Student Student

Chennai Institute of Technology

Aug 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months +)



web developer intern

unique technologies

May 2019 - Jun 2019 (2 months)

I worked as web development intern in unique technologies, chennai. Day to day responsibilites is to develop various webpages using Model View Controller(MVC) pattern.

Education



Chennai Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science 2017 - 2021

Licenses & Certifications



🌎 java - SoloLearn



Data Base Management System - NPTEL

NPTEL19CS12S31570089



Theory of Computation - NPTEL

NPTEL19CS79S21182203



Introduction to Programming Using Python - GUVI

9C18PEn9632275Ui5Q



Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4 - Coursera

6BKDWUTP97SH



Front-End JavaScript Frameworks: Angular - Coursera

AB6V3S8BC6GG



MySQL - GUVI Geek Networks, IITM Research Park m1uH29473Q951wJjo1

Skills

Python • Bootstrap • MySQL • Java • C (Programming Language) • HTML • django • Web Development • MongoDB • JavaScript